mindstick.com 2019-07-22

# Privacy & Policy

#### __  (Last updated: May 20, 2019) 

MindStick Software Pvt. Ltd. is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes our Policies and Procedures over the collection, use, disclosure, and sharing of your personal information or personal data. This Privacy Policy applies to all of our Portals including “MindStick Q&A” and “YourViews MindStick” which incorporates this Privacy Policy by reference. 

#### __  Collecting Your Personal Information 

When you create an account and profile the personal information we collect may include name, email address, location, occupation, interests, birth date, social account address, and password for the site.

The Site may collect certain information about your visit, such as the name of the Internet Service Provider and the Internet Protocol (IP) address through which you access the Internet; the date and time you access the Site; the pages that you access while at the Site and the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked directly to our site. This information is used for the operation and improvement of the Site.

#### __  Use of Your Personal Information

MindStick Software Pvt. Ltd. may use personal information to provide you with more effective customer service, to improve the Site and any related MindStick Software Pvt. Ltd. products or services, and to make the Site easier to use by eliminating the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information or by customizing the Site to your particular preference or interests.

We may use your personal information to provide you with important information about the product or service that you are using, including critical updates and notifications. Additionally, with your permission, we may send you information about other MindStick Software Pvt. Ltd. products and services, and/or share information with MindStick Software Pvt. Ltd. partners so they may send you information about their products and services.

We will only provide those companies the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

MindStick Software Pvt. Ltd. may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

(a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on MindStick Software Pvt. Ltd. or the Site;

(b) protect and defend the rights or property of MindStick Software Pvt. Ltd. and our family of Web sites; or

(c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of MindStick Software Pvt. Ltd. employees or agents, users of MindStick Software Pvt. Ltd. products or services, or members of the public.

Personal information collected on the Site may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which MindStick Software Pvt. Ltd. or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using the Site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. MindStick Software Pvt. Ltd. abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.

#### __  Access to Your Personal Information 

Customer information is collected by MindStick Software Pvt. Ltd. It is stored at MindStick Software Pvt. Ltd. hosted account secure database. You can review and edit the personal information you provided at this Site by editing your profile. You can also send email to [contact@mindstick.com](mailto:contact@mindstick.com).

#### __  Control of Your Personal Information

MindStick collects your Profile details and your submitted content, which made available for the public display. But the Profile details are selectively available (like Name, Profile Picture) for the Visitors whereas the Registered User can access more detailed information about the other registered user.

The existing user can edit and modify its Profile details at any time while logging in to the account. The user can also unsubscribe the email notification, by clicking on the unsubscribe link in the footer of the mail. 

As well as, the user can also block the ability of another MindStick user to follow you by selecting the setting for this in the user’s profile. You can also choose whether or not you follow other user.

Be aware that this privacy statement and any choices you make on the Site will not necessarily apply to personal information you may have provided to MindStick Software Pvt. Ltd. in the context of other, separately operated, MindStick Software Pvt. Ltd. products or services.

#### __  Security of Your Personal Information

The security of your information is important to us. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer servers with limited access that are located in controlled facilities. Additionally, when we transmit sensitive personal information (such as a credit card number) over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

However, no website or Internet transmission is completely secure. We urge you to take steps to keep your personal information safe, such as choosing a strong password and keeping it private, as well as logging out of your user account, and closing your web browser when finished using the MindStick Platform on a shared or unsecured device.

#### __  Communication

While establishing any communication (whether for any query/request, post editing, or sponsored post) MindStick entertain its users only through E-mails. We don’t follow any other communication medium.

MindStick don’t make any calls to its users regarding any kind of lucrative offers or for any type of Marketing and Promotion. So, beware of these types of fraudulent calls on the name of MindStick. 

#### __  Cookies

These are small files with a unique identifier that are transferred to your browser through our websites. 

They allow us to remember users who are logged in, to understand how users navigate through and use the MindStick Platform, and to display personalized content and targeted ads (including on third party sites and applications).

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of this or other web sites you visit.

#### __  Payment Information

In case of services requiring payment, we request credit card or other payment account information, which will be used solely for processing payments by the Payment Gateway Portal only. Your financial information will not be stored by us, your financial information will be stored in encrypted form on secure servers of our reputed Payment Gateway Service Provider who is beholden to treating your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy Statement.

#### __  Taxes

Subscription and access to content services fall under the purview of Service Tax as per the current indirect taxation policy, Government of India.

#### __  Legal Disclosure

Please be aware that laws in various jurisdictions in which we operate may obligate us to disclose user information and the contents of the user account to the local law enforcement authorities under a legal process or an enforceable government request. If MindStick is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its business or assets, our all existing users will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or uses of your Personal Information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your Personal Information.

#### __  Amendment in Privacy Statements

We may occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top of the privacy statement. For material changes to this privacy statement, we will notify you either by placing a prominent notice on the home page of our web site or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates.

#### __  Contact Information

MindStick Software Pvt. Ltd. welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement. If you believe that MindStick Software Pvt. Ltd. has not adhered to this privacy statement, please contact us by e-mail at [contact@mindstick.com](mailto:contact@mindstick.com) and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.

© Copyright © 2010 - 2019 MindStick Software Pvt. Ltd. All Rights Reserved
